<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Invidious on sahilister&#39;s Reimagined Doodle</title>
    <link>https://blog.sahilister.tech/tags/invidious/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Invidious on sahilister&#39;s Reimagined Doodle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 18:56:23 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.sahilister.tech/tags/invidious/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Invidious Creator Steps Away From Open Source</title>
      <link>https://blog.sahilister.tech/2020/08/invidious-creator-steps-away-from-open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 18:56:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.sahilister.tech/2020/08/invidious-creator-steps-away-from-open-source/</guid>
      <description>Recently Omar Roth, creator of Invidious, announced his stepping down from Invidious lead developer as well as open source as a whole. He cited the mental toll and other reasons for the same. This also result in shutting down of official Invidious instance, invidio.us. Invidious had largely been a one man project (though occasional contributions by others were made).
Majority of FOSS projects usually begin as hobby project or something that solved a problem faced by the creator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Invidious embed instead of Youtube&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://blog.sahilister.tech/2020/07/invidious-embed-instead-of-youtubes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 03:49:20 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.sahilister.tech/2020/07/invidious-embed-instead-of-youtubes/</guid>
      <description>When I thought about writing my blog post titled To Zinda Ho Tum, I was dilemma. Situation being, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t simply copy the poem in my blog. A simple attribution wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be enough. Then I remembered about Farhan Akhar&amp;rsquo;s narration of the poem for the movie ZKMD. I thought about embedding this video along with my thoughts on it.
Now another dilemma arouse as YouTube even in it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Privacy-Enhanced mode&amp;rdquo; embed states: &amp;gt; When you turn on privacy-enhanced mode, YouTube won&amp;rsquo;t store information about visitors on your website unless they play the video.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>